<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://underwaterl.ad/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://underwaterl.ad/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-11-19T16:13:07+00:00</updated><id>https://underwaterl.ad/feed.xml</id><title type="html">scott donaldson</title><entry><title type="html">hello and welcome to this website</title><link href="https://underwaterl.ad/2025/11/16/hello.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="hello and welcome to this website" /><published>2025-11-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-11-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://underwaterl.ad/2025/11/16/hello</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://underwaterl.ad/2025/11/16/hello.html"><![CDATA[<p>This website has been slapped together quickly. I think this is a good way to build a website. I’m using <strong><a href="https://docs.github.com/en/pages/getting-started-with-github-pages/what-is-github-pages">GitHub Pages</a></strong> and <strong><a href="https://jekyllrb.com/">Jekyll</a></strong>, neither of which I had used before. I also hadn’t used GitHub before this, which for a first-time user is freaky. Might complain about that later. The website, you might have noticed, won’t dynamically fit to anything other than a regular old PC monitor, so if you are on a mobile device and are somehow reading this, apologies - this will be fixed in the near future. There is something to be said about retrofitting dynamic markup rather than just using it to begin with I am sure, so please don’t say whatever that is.</p>

<p>Design-wise, I am reasonably happy with the site, if you care. The fixed-sidebar-with-stuff-on-the-right is I think the tried and true way to do personal websites if you want to seem mysterious and cool. I’m imagining a spectrum with this on one side and a 2004-era MySpace page on the other. We can add a Y axis later and go nuts with it maybe. I’ll tweak lots of things here and there in the near term, to the site I mean. Maybe the tweaking will last forever.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: this is not an advertisement. I have a <strong><a href="https://scottdonaldson.bigcartel.com/">store</a></strong>, which has served as my de facto personal website for a couple of years. That’ll be gone shortly and replaced by Blessed Shopify Integration right here. The service subscriptions will overlap for some months but I won’t let that get in the way of my disdain for Big Cartel. Unrelated, but I am going to start relentlessly promoting my <strong><a href="www.inprnt.com/gallery/underwaterlad/">Inprnt store</a></strong> because I feel like I’ve banked up enough goodwill by not relentlessly promoting it over the past three years.</p>

<p>The blog-portion (the “log” - see previously-mentioned desire to seem mysterious and cool) of this website I am going to treat more like a journal rather than the ThoughtCatalog-like nonsense of the short-lived Substack and the How-To-lite wastes of time of the short-lived Patreon. There will be things about art but it’s not going to be “about art”. Look at the websites <strong><a href="https://webring.xxiivv.com/">here</a></strong> for example. It’s a great list of some pretty great websites. I think I will from time to time post and talk about my favourite art pieces, which is something I’ve never done before, partly because I like art for nonsophisticated reasons and partly because it’s really hard to put into words why I like that art. But if turning vibes into words isn’t the point of writing, I don’t know what is.</p>

<p>Music I have been listening to lately:</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://peaceville.bandcamp.com/album/still-life-remastered">Opeth - Still Life</a></strong><br />
<strong><a href="https://geometriclullaby.bandcamp.com/album/perfect-fake-2">アバドン - Perfect Fake 2</a></strong><br />
<strong><a href="https://hethe.bandcamp.com/album/control-your-souls-desire-for-freedom">HEATHE - Control Your Soul’s Desire For Freedom</a></strong></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This website has been slapped together quickly. I think this is a good way to build a website. I’m using GitHub Pages and Jekyll, neither of which I had used before. I also hadn’t used GitHub before this, which for a first-time user is freaky. Might complain about that later. The website, you might have noticed, won’t dynamically fit to anything other than a regular old PC monitor, so if you are on a mobile device and are somehow reading this, apologies - this will be fixed in the near future. There is something to be said about retrofitting dynamic markup rather than just using it to begin with I am sure, so please don’t say whatever that is.]]></summary></entry></feed>